joltonline.com 2011-12-31

# Privacy | Jolt Online Gaming

## Privacy Policy

#### Jolt Online Gaming Limited has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to privacy.

Jolt Online Gaming Limited and its subsidiaries, parent companies, joint ventures and other corporate entities under common ownership (together “Jolt”, “we”, “our” and “us”) respect and protect your right to privacy in relation to your use of websites and applications (including games) operated by Jolt (the “Applications”). These include, amongst others, the social games developed and published by Jolt, such as Utopia Kingdoms, Playboy Party and Jolt Poker.

We have adopted the following policies to safeguard your personal information and to protect its confidentiality. Please ensure that you read this Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions [www.joltonline.com/terms/] before using any Applications.  If you do not read or if you disagree with any aspect of the Privacy Policy or the Terms and Conditions, you should not use any of the Applications.  By accepting our Privacy Policy in registration or installation, you consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy

If you access any Applications from a third party social network site (such as www.facebook.com) you may also be required to accept the terms of use and the privacy policy of that third party site.

#### What information do we collect about you?

At Jolt, we collect personal information and non-personal information. The types of information we collect depend on the nature of your interaction with us. You may choose not to provide us with your personal information. However, if you make this choice we may not be able to provide you with the product, service, or information that you requested.

Personal information – Personal information is information that can identify an individual or information about an identifiable individual. We may collect personal information including the following:

  * Contact information – your name, postal address, telephone number and email address
  * Personal preferences – opinions, interests, hobbies, product wish lists, language preferences, and marketing consent; and
  * Financial information and transaction information – products purchased, method of payment, amount paid, and credit or debit card number.

Non-personal information – Non-personal information does not identify you as an individual. For example, we may collect certain non-personal data when you visit our Applications, such as your Internet Protocol address, the type and version of browser you are using or the referring URL; or we may collect and summarize customer information in a non-personal, aggregate format for statistical and research purposes.

#### How do we collect information from you?

#### We collect information from you by three main means:

  * Information we collect from you directly
  * Information about you received from www.facebook.com
  * Information we collect automatically

#### Information we collect from you directly

When you register for an Application, whether directly or indirectly, we may request you to provide us with the following information, which we will collect and store:

  * Your age or birthday
  * Your first and last names
  * Your e-mail address
  * A password and other information that helps us confirm that it is you accessing your account

#### Information about you received from www.facebook.com

When you use or access any Applications through www.facebook.com, you allow us to access certain information from your profile for that site. The information you allow us to access is affected by the privacy settings you establish at www.facebook.com. You can control and find out more about these settings at www.facebook.com. For example, we may access and store some or all of the following information, as allowed by you and your preferences:

  * Your first and last name
  * Your profile picture or its URL
  * Your user ID number, which is linked to publically available information such as name and profile photo
  * The user ID numbers for your friends that are also connected to our game(s)
  * The login e-mail you provided to www.facebook.com when you registered
  * Your physical location and that of your access devices
  * Your gender
  * Your birthday

By accessing any of our Applications through www.facebook.com, you are authorizing us to collect, store, and use in accordance with this Privacy Policy any and all information that you agreed www.facebook.com could provide to us through the www.facebook.com Application Programming Interface (“API”). Your agreement takes place when you “accept” or “allow” (or similar terms) one of our applications on www.facebook.com.

#### Information Jolt Collects Automatically

When you use our Applications, we may collect the Internet Protocol (IP) address of your computer and of your Internet service provider, the date and time you access our Applications, the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our Applications, the computer operating system you are using, the sections of our Applications you visit and use, the website pages read and images viewed, and the content you download from the Applications. This information is used for website and system administration purposes and to improve the Applications.

  * Cookies – Jolt may use cookies to store your individual preferences and system information. “Cookies” are small electronic data files that websites can store on your computer for record keeping purposes. Cookies also may be used on the Applications for other reasons, such as to limit the number of times you have to enter a password or enter your language preference, to offer personalized web page content and information for your use, and to track your activity on the Applications. The use of cookies is standard in the Internet industry and many websites use them. In addition, you may modify your browser’s settings to notify you whenever a website is going to deposit a cookie on your computer’s hard drive or other storage media. The notification option generally gives you the opportunity to decide whether to accept or refuse a cookie in each instance. You can configure your browser to always disable cookies when cookies are being sent to your computer.
  * Website Tracking Information – Web beacons are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of web users. We may use web beacons (sometimes called “clear gifs”, “web bugs” or “pixel tags”) to compile tracking information reports regarding website user demographics, website traffic patterns, and website purchases. We may then provide these reports to advertisers and others. None of the tracking information in these reports can be connected to the identities or other personal information of individual users. In addition, we may use web beacons in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by the recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. If you do not want to receive these emails, please see the “unsubscribe” section below. For Jolt’s own research purposes we may link tracking information with personal information voluntarily provided by users of our Applications. Once such a link is made, all of the linked information is treated as personal information and will be used and disclosed only in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

From time to time we may supplement information you give us with information from other sources, such as information validating your address or other available information you have provided to us. This is to help us maintain the accuracy of the information we collect and to help us provide better service.

#### How do we use your personal information?

The primary reason we collect personal information from you is to provide you with a better gaming experience. We will typically use this information for the following:

  * To register you on any Application;
  * To allow you use any Application, including playing any game;
  * To administer Applications and to resolve technical problems;
  * To customise your experience of using the Applications;
  * To improve game play and Application functionality;
  * To provide technical support and respond to user inquiries;
  * To prevent fraud or potentially illegal activities;
  * To enforce terms of use;
  * To notify you of improvements and changes to Applications;
  * To rank players on their achievements and to display those achievements to all users;
  * To encourage input and feedback from you to improve our products and services;
  * To collect fees; and
  * To analyze trends and user traffic and gather statistical information

We also use your personal information for other, secondary reasons, including:

  * Customer service
  * To administer a loyalty program, including but not limited to tracking and analyzing your purchases and preferences to better understand your product and service needs and eligibility
  * To facilitate your acceptance of offers made by our third party marketing partners
  * To tailor our online content based on your preferences
  * To measure and improve the effectiveness of our Applications or our marketing endeavours
  * To offer and promote additional products and services we offer
  * For other purposes as described in this Privacy Policy
  * As otherwise provided or required by law

#### Does Jolt share your information?

Jolt does not sell, rent or share your personal information to any third party except as described in this Privacy Policy.

  * Marketing Partners – if you accept an offer from any of our third party marketing partners, we will share your information with that specific third party, in accordance with the terms of the offer. If you have previously requested that your personal information not be shared with third parties, but then later consent by accepting a third party marketing offer available through one of our Applications, we will share your contact and billing information with that specific third party, in accordance with the terms of the offer.  
Some of these operations may result in personal information collected by Jolt being stored or processed outside of Ireland and, as a result, your personal information may be accessible to law enforcement and regulatory authorities in accordance with the law of these foreign jurisdictions.
  * Service Providers – Jolt may use third parties to manage one of more aspects of our business operations, including the processing or handling of personal information. We may share personal information with such third parties to perform services on our behalf such as fulfilling online orders, processing non-cash payments, sending marketing communications, servicing products, conducting research surveys, verifying and validating information that you have provided to us, delivering products, and providing customer support services. When we do use an outside company, we use contractual and other appropriate means to ensure that your personal information is used in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.  
Jolt has taken precautions to prevent the fraudulent use of your information on our Applications. Jolt has adopted industry standard authentication procedures to ensure your protection while shopping with us online. This includes, but is not limited to, contacting financial institutions or credit reporting agencies to ensure the authenticity of your credit card and to validate your credit card billing information.
  * Jolt, its corporate parents, affiliates, subsidiaries and divisions – Jolt may share personal information gathered on our Applications amongst our corporate parents, subsidiaries, affiliates or divisions for internal business purposes in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If Jolt shares your information within its corporate family, we will ensure that your information continues to be used only in accordance with this Privacy Policy and your expressed choices.
  * Licensees – if you use any of our Services where we use intellectual property licensed from a third party, we may request your permission to share your information with that specific third party. If you give that consent, we will share your information with that specific third party. If you have previously requested that your personal information not be shared with third parties, but then later consent, we will share your personal information information with that specific third party.  
Some of these operations may result in personal information collected by Jolt being stored or processed outside of Ireland and, as a result, your personal information may be accessible to law enforcement and regulatory authorities in accordance with the law of these foreign jurisdictions.
  * Sale or Transfer of Business or Assets of Jolt – Any information we have about you may be transferred or disclosed to a purchaser or prospective purchaser in the event of a sale, assignment, or other transfer of all or a portion of our business or assets. Should such a transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to ensure that the transferee uses your information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.
  * Legal Disclosure – Jolt may disclose your information as permitted or required by law or to comply with any legal process, as well as to protect and defend the rights of Jolt and/or our customers.

#### How does Jolt protect your information?

The file containing your personal information will be stored on our servers and will only be accessible to our employees and those of our agents and service providers who require it in the course of their duties. Jolt takes appropriate steps to protect your personal information. We maintain appropriate safeguards and current security standards to protect your personal information against unauthorized access, disclosure, or misuse. For example, electronic records are stored in secure, limited-access servers; electronic data is stored behind secured encryption access; we use technological tools like firewalls and passwords; and we ensure our employees are trained on the importance of maintaining the security and confidentiality of personal information.

SSL Technology – Our Applications use encryption technology, such as Secure Sockets Layer (“SSL”), to protect your personal information during data transport. SSL encrypts ordering information such as your name, address, and credit card number.

Although we cannot take responsibility for any theft, misuse, unauthorized disclosure, loss, alteration or destruction of data by a third party, we take reasonable precautions to prevent such occurrences.

#### How can you verify your information?

You may check your information to verify, update, or correct it, and to have any obsolete information removed. You can ask to review any of the information that we have retained, how we have used it, and to whom we have disclosed it at any time by contacting us as indicated below under the heading “Contacting Jolt”. Subject to certain exceptions prescribed by law, and provided we can authenticate your identity, you will be given reasonable access to your personal information, and will be entitled to challenge the accuracy and completeness of the information and to have it amended as appropriate. You may also ask us to change your preferences regarding how we use or disclose your information, or let us know that you do not wish to receive any further communication from us.

#### When is your information removed?

We keep your information only as long as we need it for legitimate business purposes and to meet any legal requirements. We have retention standards that meet these parameters. We destroy your information when it is no longer needed, or we remove your personally identifiable information to render it anonymous.

#### Links to third party websites

Our Applications may contain links that permit you to link to other websites or Internet resources. When you click on one of those links you are connecting to another website or Internet resource. Jolt has no responsibility or liability for, or control over, those other websites or Internet resources or their collection, use and disclosure of your personal information. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of those other websites before you submit any personal information to them.

#### Contacting Jolt

If you have any questions, concerns or complaints about the privacy practices of our organization please contact us at the following:

Email: info@joltonline.com (please read the Important Reminder below)

You may contact a member of the senior management team by calling +353 1 672 9626 or you can contact us in writing addressed to Jolt Online Gaming Ltd., 6-7 St Stephen’s Green, Dublin 2, IRELAND

We will respond to your request or investigate your concern as quickly as we can, but no later than 40 days from the date of receipt of your query.

Important Reminder about email communications: Please remember that email sent over the Internet is not secure. If you send an email directly to us from your own email account the contents will not be encrypted. We strongly recommend that you do not send sensitive information (like a credit card number) to us via unencrypted email. Jolt is not responsible for any transmission by you of any personal information over the Internet.

#### Disclaimer

JOLT, ITS DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, SERVANTS AND AGENTS, AFFILIATES OR OTHER REPRESENTATIVES AND THEIR RESPECTIVE PARENT AND SUBSIDIARY COMPANIES, SHALL NOT BE LIABLE IN RESPECT OF ANY CLAIMS, EMERGENCIES, DEMANDS, CAUSES OF ACTION, DAMAGES, LOSSES, EXPENSES, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION, REASONABLE LEGAL FEES AND COSTS OF PROCEEDINGS ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE AND/OR DISSEMINATION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION RELATING TO YOU IN ACCORDANCE WITH THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT AND YOUR CONSENTS.

#### Will this privacy policy change?

Last Update: 11-04-2011

To accommodate changes in our services, changes in technology, and legal developments, this Privacy Policy may change over time without notice to you. We may add, change, or remove portions of the Privacy Policy when we feel it is appropriate to do so. We encourage you to review our Privacy Policy periodically. Each time you submit personal information or use our services you agree to be bound by the then current terms of the Privacy Policy. Whenever we update the Privacy Policy we will change the date to indicate when the changes were made.
